MOHSAN



Contact

Address:

Post Code N18 2QY

Phone:

+447459108614

Email:

Sharmohsan2@gmail.com

Languages

English Urdu Sindhi

Hobbies

Watching Sports

Playing Cricket

Watching News

Reading Literature Books

Summary

Remarkable experience in designing high power electronics. Sound knowledge of electronic hardware design and its life cycle. Immense ability to resolve all electronics engineering problems in the designing process. Good skills to maintain electrical safety standards in the facility.

Have excellent Knowledge and skills about C++, Python, Image process, OOP, Matlab , Engineering project Management & Arduino.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Collaboration and Team work
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

Graphic Designing Course

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

- Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator
- · The Art & Practice of Planning and Projecting

Legal Research

Sep 2021 - Aug 2022

Hand Written Text Recognition Using Deep Learning

Education

Masters

University of law (London) 2023

B.S Electronics

Quaid-i-Azam University, Islamabad 2018 – 2022

Intermediate (Science)

Cadet College, Ghotki 2016 – 2017

References

Prof: Dr: Hasan Mahmood

Quaid-i-Azam University, Islamabad

Email: hasan@qau.edu.pk

Telephone: +92-51 9064-3132

Assistant Prof: Dr: Naeem Ali Bhatti

Quaid-i-Azam University, Islamabad

Email: nbhatti@gau.edu.pk

Telephone: +92-51 9064-3216

